cmpmedica.com 2012-04-18

# UBM Medica : Privacy Policy

Thank you for using www.ubmmedica.com **(the "Website")**. We are committed to protecting your right to privacy as a consumer of our online services. Please read the following Privacy Policy to understand how we use and protect the information that you provide to us. By using and continuing to use this Website, you consent to the collection, use and transfer of your information under the terms of this Privacy Policy. 

If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not provide your personal details to us. We may need to update this Privacy Policy from time to time and when we do so we will place a notice on the Website to indicate this has happened. We recommend that you regularly check this page to ensure that you have read the most recent version. 

In this Privacy Policy, " **UBM Medica** " means UBM Medica Limited (registered company number:00370721). The address from which we provide these online services is: UBM Medica, Ludgate House, 245 Blackfriars Road, London SE1 9UY. 

The information you provide to us will be held on [UBM Medica](http://www.ubmmedica.com/) computers that are based in the UK. [UBM Medica](http://www.cmpedica.com/) processes personal data in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998. This Privacy Policy only relates to the Website service and does not extend to your use of the Internet outside of the Website. 

**DataCollection**

**What data do we collect?**

The data we collect within the Website is to enable us to communicate directly with you about your specific business requirements. This includes your name, contact details. This is your personal information. 

We will collect, use or disclose your personal information if permitted by law or required to do so by law or where we believe such action is necessary in order to protect or defend us or other third parties against error, negligence, breach of contract, theft fraud and other illegal or harmful activity, to comply with our audit and security requirements, and to audit compliance with our corporate policies, procedures, legal and contractual obligations. Your personal card data will not be stored alongside your other personal data and will only be accessed for the purpose of processing refunds in a secure and controlled basis. 

**What do we do with it?**

The personal information you provide within the Website is used as follows: 

  * to communicate with you about all UBM Medica services 
  * to provide you with access to all parts of our Website and to supply the goods or services you have requested 
  * to tell you about changes in our services or about features we think you may find interesting 

In the event of a sale, merger, consolidation, change in control, transfer of substantial assets, reorganisation or liquidation, we may transfer, sell, or assign to third parties information concerning your relationship with us, including without limitation, personally identifiable information that you provide and other information concerning your relationship with us. In addition, to maintaincustomer service standards and to assist staff training, we may record and monitor incoming calls. Unless required to do so by law, we will not otherwise share, sell or distribute any of the information you provide to us without your consent. 

**Our commitment to security**

We have taken all appropriate action to safeguard and prevent unauthorised access to personal data, to maintain data security and to ensure that the information we collect online is used only in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998 and for the purpose(s) outlined above. However, due to the open communication nature of the Internet, we cannot guarantee that communications between you and us, or information stored on our servers, will be free from unauthorised access by third parties. 

For further information or to edit your personal information please contact: [phill.callow@ubm.com](http://www.ubmmedica.com/#mce_temp_url#)
